CAROLINA CIOLIN

Web Developer | Front-end | HTML | CSS | Figma | Git Beimerstetten, Germany | carolinaciolin@gmail.com | +49 0176 70378143 | +353 86 120 9094

SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer proficient in HTML and CSS, and experienced with Git and Figma. I am currently studying to further develop my skills in the area.

I hold a Bachelor's degree in Art History and a Specialization in Animation. Strong interest in digital art and design with several courses and certifications in the area, including Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign (Adobe Certified Professional).

My previous work experiences include:

- Over 10 years in customer service;
- Over 10 years in administration;
- 1.5 years working in the hospitality sector in Dublin during an English exchange program;
- Human resources;
- Training;
- Inventory;
- Creating formulas, tables and indexes in Excel.

*EU Citizen - Eligible for full-time employment in Europe

To check my work please access:



Bē behance.net/carolinaciolin



github.com/CarolinaCiolin

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer

since 2018

Creation of logos, Instagram posts, business cards and illustrations.

Exchange Student (Ireland) feb 2022 - jul 2023

During my career break, I studied English in Ireland, enriching my language skills and cultural understanding. At the same time, I worked part-time as a waitress and kitchen assistant, improving my interpersonal skills.

Administrative Analyst

Proguaru · jul 2018 - nov 2021

- · Working in the areas of Attendance, Cleaning of Public Buildings, Access Control and Assets;
- · Development of monthly indices and reports (attendance, expenditure on overtime, absences and delays, balance of contracts, among others);

- Development of a satisfaction survey regarding the services provided, with subsequent analysis and proposal of improvements;
- Development and delivery of training such as: Conflict Management, Cleaning Procedure in Healthcare Environments and Quality Control Program;
- Acting in various intersectoral working groups as secretary and member, including: Uniform Procurement, Materials Inventory, Property Inventory, Implementation of Sustainable Practices, Contract Management, among others;
- Creation of procedure manuals (Customer Service, Cleaning in Healthcare Environments and Contract Management);
- Handling, controlling and feeding administrative processes;
- Control of company assets with more than ten locations using a system and spreadsheets;
- Creation of Excel spreadsheets to structure the expansion of the Assets sector;
- Registration of new assets and transfer of location and responsibility;
- · Organizing the Inventory of Assets, dealing with any discrepancies found and preparing the final report.

Customer Service Analyst Proguaru · feb 2021 - jul 2018

- Receiving and assisting residents, suppliers and workers, answering questions, providing guidance on the services offered and making the relevant referrals.
- · Updating the registration details of clients, suppliers, workers and other people who come to the office, and forwarding them to the relevant departments.
- · Answering the telephone and managing incoming and requested calls.
- · Providing employees with forms for requests related to the human resources sector, guiding them through the procedure and filling them in. For example: requesting/amending/canceling transportation vouchers, food vouchers, basic food baskets, life insurance, among others.
- · Answering questions regarding payroll.
- · Scheduling INSS medical examinations for employees, providing the necessary guidance on the entire process, as well as return to work.
- · Reception of new employees, advising them on salary, benefits and list of documents for admission. Checking documents and taking them to the induction exam and integration.
- · Recording customer service, suggestions and complaints (made in person, by email, telephone and WhatsApp) in a dedicated system. Forwarding to the appropriate department and following up until resolution. E.g. fixing potholes and manholes, cleaning public areas such as streets, squares and streams, and removing dead animals.
- · Responsible for creating monthly indices for the Service Sector using various graphs, for statistical purposes, with the aim of improving the quality of service.
- · Receiving and filing various documents delivered to the service department, or received via e-mail, and forwarding them to the responsible sectors.
- · Attending to residents with overdue payments, negotiating their debts using the system.
- \cdot Responsible for carrying out administrative activities, seeking to understand and carry them out in accordance with company procedures.

Front-end Developer (Internship) Kanui · jun 2013 - dec 2013

Creation and optimization of web pages using HTML and CSS.

School Agent

Prefeitura Municipal de Guarulhos · feb 2011 - jun 2013

- · Coordinating the movement of students in and out of the school, during classes and breaks.
- · Assisting the school management in coordinating shifts;
- Routing and monitoring students when they are involved in extra-class and extracurricular activities;

- Receiving and delivering internal and external correspondence;
- Assisting the teacher in the classroom;
- Referring situations that put student safety at risk to the school management;
- Operating computer equipment and systems;
- Participation in the production of the bimonthly newspaper of EPG Rachel de Queiroz, being responsible for photos, layout, writing and proofreading.

Administrative Assistant

Austera Seguros · jun 2009 - feb 2011

- · Receiving telephone calls;
- Registering insurance policies in the system;
- · Monthly separation of insurance due and forwarding to the broker responsible;
- Collecting overdue installments.

EDUCATION

Postgraduate Diploma in Animation

Senac · 2017-2021

Bachelor of Art History

Universidade Federal de São Paulo · 2011-2015

Information Technology

Eniac · 2006-2008

CERTIFICATES

- · Adobe Certified Professional in Visual Design Using Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Certified Professional in Graphic Design & Illustration Using Adobe Illustrator
- · Adobe Certified Professional in Print & Digital Media Publication Using Adobe InDesign
- · Adobe Photoshop for Illustration
- Cambridge First Certification in English Level: B2
- EF SET English Certificate Level: C2
- · Knowledge Multipliers
- · Customer Service

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese native
- · English fluent
- · German basic